Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) Audiovisual Materials
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Digital Video
  - News Briefs, 2007-2012
    - U-M President Mary Sue Coleman 2011, .mov file; President Coleman's remarks at the U-M 2011 Spring Commencement.
    - U-M professor looks at river and lakes in a flume 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan researcher Bradley Cardinale explains why looking at river and lakes in small flumes 150 times, explains how nature works.
    - U-M professors reach out to Northern Michigan through Traverse City Film Festival 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan professors, serve as jurors, moderators and lead discussions for the Traverse City Film Festival.
    - U-M reaches northward 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan professors serve as jurors, moderators and lead discussions for the Traverse City Film Festival. U-M profs help choose winners at Traverse City Film Festival.
    - U-M Speaks Out Ken Lieberthal on Chinese currency 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan professor Emeritus speaks about the Chinese currency manipulation and the ways to tackle it.
    - U-M Symphony Band looks back 2011, .mp4 file; U-M planning team for Symphony Band's trip to China elaborate on what went into getting ready for the trip and their memories of the trip. Planners talk about how the planning and the China Trip video with 3 interviews
    - UMAPS scholars share their experiences 2011, .mp4 file; African scholars from South Africa, Ghana and Liberia share why UMAPS at University of Michigan was a memorable experience for their research, growth and development.
    - U-M's bold cultural initiative 2011, .mov file; University Symphony Band breaks new ground as faculty and students announce China tour.
    - UMS presents a new season 2011, .mp4 file; The new season of University Musical Society showcases the last staging of Einstein on the Beach, special Chinese performances and more. UMS is looking East interview with Michael Kodziolka.
    - Understanding Patent Law 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan Gerald R. Ford School associate professor Shobita R. Parthasarathy talks about patent law and its role in genetics and biotechnology.
    - United we stand: Democrats seek to unify party, attract voters during their national convention 2011, .mov file; U-M professor Vincent Hutchings talks about the 2008 Democratic Party convention.
    - University of Michigan offers 22 ways to think about food 2011, .mp4 file; New Sophomore Initiative at the University of Michigan College of Literature, Science, and the Arts offers a new way and a multidisciplinary approach to food.
    - University of Michigan professor discusses the new flu strain 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan professor Arnold Monto talks about the new flu strain.
    - University of Michigan researcher discovers prehistoric clue 2011, .mp4 file; University of Michigan anthropologist John O'Shea discovers a prehistoric wooden object at the bottom of Lake Huron.
    - Unrest in the Middle East 2011, .mp4 file; Nadine Naber, an assistant professor of women's studies and American culture, and Philip Potter, an assistant professor of public policy and political science, talk about Middle East issues. U-M experts discuss Egypt President Hosni Mubarak, media Video interview with Nadine Naber, women's studies, public policy.
    - US and China Relations 2011, .mp4 file; Ken Lieberthal decodes US and China relations.
    - Violence and brain injury 2011, .mp3 file; University of Michigan School of Public Health researcher Stoddard's research shows a link between violent behavior and brain injury in youth.
    - Wallenberg Lecture 2011, .mp3 file; Annual lecture for the Wallenberg medal delivered by Aung San Suu Kyi Aung San Suu Kyi delivers the Wallenberg lecture.
    - What makes a great speech? 2011, .mp3 file; University of Michigan's Sara Forsdyke finds out if the current presidential candidates are great orators.
    - Why did Borders fail? 2011, .mp3 file; University of Michigan Marketing professor Aradhna Krishna talks about the reasons that led to Borders failure and bankruptcy. U-M marketing professor discusses the reasons podcast with Aradhna Krishna.
    - University of Michigan Graduate exhibit 2012, .flv and .mp4 files; A first-hand look at how artists prepared for annual exhibit and the various venues for the show.
    - Weibo Promotional Videos - Alumni Lookout: Many Michigan M's, 2012 2012, .mp4 file; Promotional video about the University of Michigan created by News Service for the Chinese social media platform, Weibo and also for the University of Michigan Alumni Association's Alumni Lookout, a virtual window into campus. This video is a montage of images with the iconic block M from around the campus and Ann Arbor and concludes with a welcome to alumni.
    - Weibo Promotional Videos - College of Engineering, 2012 2012, .mp4 file; Promotional video about the University of Michigan created by News Service for the Chinese social media platform, Weibo. This video introduces students and faculty of the College of Engineering and highlights prominent student groups, research projects, and facilities.
    - Weibo Promotional Videos - College of Literature, Science and the Arts, 2012 2012, .mp4 file; Promotional video about the University of Michigan created by News Service for the Chinese social media platform, Weibo. This video introduces students and faculty of the College of Literature, Science, and the Arts as well as its research collections, facilities and laboratories, and unique cultural opportunities.
    - Weibo Promotional Videos - The Michigan Difference, 2012 2012, .mp4 file; Promotional video about the University of Michigan created by News Service for the Chinese social media platform, Weibo. This video defines 'the Michigan Difference' through the university's academic, cultural, and athletic accomplishments.
    - Weibo Promotional Videos - 'Welcome Back', 2012 2012, .mp4 file; Promotional video about the University of Michigan created by News Service for the Chinese social media platform, Weibo. This video highlights the diversity of the Ann Arbor campus and the various opportunities available to students; includes appearances by President Mary Sue Coleman and Head Football Coach Brady Hoke.